[{"answer": "Well, the problem is several things.", "docId": "121128pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "What's wrong with that?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "Well, because it's false hope.", "docId": "121128pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "And what is wrong with giving the poorer sections, the needier sections of society a bit of hope and even if for most of them it turns out in the end to be a hope that isn't realized?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "Well, we actually do know it.", "docId": "121128pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "You've got no way of knowing, have you?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "I mean, you make it sound wonderfully harmless.", "docId": "121128pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "And I guarantee, most everybody realizes I probably won't win tonight, but what if?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "It's -- government gambling has been a failed revenue source across the country, whether it's Massachusetts, California, you name it.", "docId": "121128pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "Now that is a huge chunk of change, isn't it?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "But if you have sales -- that money comes from $4.7 billion worth of sales.", "docId": "121128pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "What is actually your problem with that?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "Well, I'm going to sidebar for just a second on you and then come back to that if I can.", "docId": "121128pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "Which one should I do?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "And there's 175 million that'll be watching -- I hope your ratings were that good tomorrow night -- that didn't win.", "docId": "121128pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "I mean, there's got to be somebody tomorrow possibly who'll be re-watching this avidly as I'm sure they do every night, and saying, Dave Ramsey, I just won half a billion dollars, you know, what are you talking about?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "Well, I think there's a lot of theories out there running around and you know I've got the formal education in finance degree and so I've studied economics like a lot of folks have, and I was formally schooled in Keynesian economics.", "docId": "121128pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "Does America suffer when taxes are slightly higher in terms of its economic prosperity, or is that just a bit of a myth?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "At some point, of course, there is such a thing as too much tax.", "docId": "121128pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "Steven Rattner, is there a principle or is it just bloody minded news now by Republicans led by Grover Norquist, we shall not pay anymore taxes ever?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "Broadly speaking, here's where I think this has to end up.", "docId": "121128pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "Putting your pragmatic hats on, if you were in that negotiating room, Emil Henry, what would the deal be?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "I would say you need to have a compromise that's more in the middle.", "docId": "121128pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "Steven Rattner, if you were in that room and that was on the table what would you say?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "It is a tax on the poorer and the numbers bare that out.", "docId": "121128pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "Is this becoming a tax on the poor?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "It is a gimmick.", "docId": "121128pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "I mean, it's a gimmick, isn't it?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "MILEY: Not at all.", "docId": "121128pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "Were you surprised?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, my preference, my preference is for the president to be more progressive.", "docId": "121128pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "What should they be thinking now?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "Jobs, jobs, jobs, and jobs with a living wage.", "docId": "121128pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "And very quickly, what's the number one priority to try and eradicate poverty, would you say?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "Well, I've got to tell you honestly, Piers, I've been doing this almost 23 years, and there has been nothing but goodness coming as far as I can see.", "docId": "121128pmt", "aSentId": 566, "question": "Do you appreciate that, too?", "qSentId": 565}, {"answer": "Nobody in the New York Lottery can play.", "docId": "121128pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "And Yolanda, are you allowed to play the lottery or not?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "Oh, I think I won $250 in the state of Georgia.", "docId": "121128pmt", "aSentId": 585, "question": "What is the biggest amount of money you've won on a scratch card?", "qSentId": 584}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121128pmt", "aSentId": 588, "question": "You decided not to retire?", "qSentId": 587}, {"answer": "I think right now -- I mean I've always thought I'd buy an exotic island or a bunch of cars for friends and family.", "docId": "121128pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "If you won -- obviously, I know you can't, I'm talking metaphorically, if you won a half a billion dollars, as the Powerball now is tonight what would you spend it on?", "qSentId": 592}]